<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home Page on Ventus Docs</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/</link><description>Recent content in Home Page on Ventus Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 04:20:36 +0430</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/terms-and-conditions/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/terms-and-conditions/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Diese Datenschutzerklärung informiert Sie über die Art, den Umfang und Zweck der Verarbeitung von personenbezogenen Daten (nachfolgend „Daten“) innerhalb des Onlineangebotes der Ventus Cloud AG (im Folgenden „wir“ bzw. „uns“) und der mit ihm verbundenen Webseiten, Funktionen und Inhalte sowie externen Onlinepräsenzen, wie z.B. unserer Social Media Profile auf (nachfolgend gemeinsam bezeichnet als „Onlineangebot“). Die nachfolgende Datenschutzrichtlinie ist auf die Ventus Cloud AG anwendbar.
Verantwortlicher Firma
Ventus Cloud AG</description></item><item><title>Terms and Conditions</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/terms-and-conditions/terms-and-conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/terms-and-conditions/terms-and-conditions/</guid><description>General Terms and Conditions of Ventus Cloud AG
Geltungsbereich Diese allgemeinen Geschäftsbedingungen (AGB) gelten für alle Geschäftsbeziehungen zwischen dem Kunden und der Ventus Cloud AG (Ventus). Vertragsgrundlage ist jeweils die zum Zeitpunkt des Vertragsschlusses gültige Fassung der AGB sowie die Ventus Cloud AG Datenschutzerklärung ventuscloud.eu/de/privacy und die aktuelle Preisliste der Ventus Dienstleistungen ventuscloud.eu/de/pricing welche integrierende Bestandteile der AGB bilden. Abweichende oder ergänzende allgemeine Geschäftsbedingungen des Kunden werden selbst bei Kenntnis von Ventus nicht Vertragsbestandteil der Geschäftsbeziehung mit dem Kunden, ausser Ventus hat diesen ausdrücklich schriftlich zugestimmt.</description></item><item><title>Account</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/account/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create and manage a new user account in teh Cloud Console.
Table of contents Registration Manage Account  Edit Account Change password Set authenticator Find all sessions Login and Logout Registration To start work in the Cloud Console, firstly, you need to register a new account, for this do the following:
follow the Authorization page of the Cloud Console - console.</description></item><item><title>Devops as a Service</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/terms-and-conditions/devops-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/terms-and-conditions/devops-as-a-service/</guid><description>Leistungsbeschreibung &amp;amp; zusätzliche Bedingungen DevOps-as-a-Service ist eine DevOps-Tool-Umgebung für eine container-basierte Software-Entwicklung. Der Kunde erhält über Ventus Cloud Console Zugriff auf nachfolgende DevOps-Funktionen.
Leistungsbeschreibung &amp;amp; zusätzliche Bedingungen DEVOPS-AS-A-SERVICE
Stand: 25.11.2020 Version: 1
Funktionen DevOps-Funktionen Die Ventus Cloud stellt dem Kunden nachfolgende DevOps-Funktionen innerhalb einer Tool-Umgebung bereit. Die Ventus Cloud ist frei, durch welche Software-Tools in welcher Version die DevOpsFunktionen realisiert werden. Folgend ist der aktuelle Stand von DevOps-Funktionen und Software-Tools dargestellt:</description></item><item><title>Installation OpenStack CLI</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/tutorials-advanced/installation-openstack-cli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/tutorials-advanced/installation-openstack-cli/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to install OpenStack CLI on Linux VM in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Prerequisites Install OpenStack CLI on Ubuntu VM Install OpenStack CLI on Centos VM Prerequisites In this article we will assume, that we have already created the following resources, that refer to the Project named dev1, that was created in the Organization named Test-Shop:</description></item><item><title>K8S Cluster</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/kubernetes/kubernetes-cluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/kubernetes/kubernetes-cluster/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, resize, delete Kubernetes Cluster and instructions for other steps to manage Kubernetes Cluster in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Clusters Page Create Cluster Cluster details page Download kubeconfig file Resize Cluster Delete Cluster Clusters page To get to the Clusters page, select the Clusters from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu: On this page you can find all created Kubernetes Clusters in the current Project of the selected Organization, with their Headers, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Cluster: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions:</description></item><item><title>Object Storage</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/object-storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/object-storage/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of what is Object Storage in Cloud Console, how to create, delete buckets and instructions for other steps to manage an Object Storage in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Introduction Use Object Storage with Python API Creating connection Listing buckets Creating bucket Creating object Listing bucket content Changing object ACL Generating object download-URL Deleting object Deleting bucket Use Object Storage with S3 Browser Introduction The Cloud Console Object Storage makes it possible to store data simply and cost-effectively.</description></item><item><title>Ventus Console 2.5.6</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/release-notes/ventus-console2.5.6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/release-notes/ventus-console2.5.6/</guid><description> Successfully delivered to Production: 28.04.2021
Ventus Console 2.5.6 was successfully delivered to Production.
Here are the list of updates:
Console:
Newsfeed Additional VM actions in the menu Error details for VMs and Clusters in ERROR status Allow all Unicode characters in entity names: Cluster Auto-scaling and private network access settings Miscellaneous fixes and improvements Admin console:
Users list with pagination and filters</description></item><item><title>Virtual Machines</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/compute/virtual-machines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/compute/virtual-machines/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, resize, delete Linux and Windows Virtual Machine, and instructions for other steps to manage Virtual Machines in Cloud Console.
Table of contents Virtual Machines Page Create Linux Virtual Machine Create Windows Virtual Machine Virtual Machine details page Download RDP File Edit Virtual Machine Resize Virtual Machine Delete Virtual Machine Virtual Machines page To get to the Virtual Machines page, select the Virtual Machines from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu: On this page you can find all created Virtual Machines in the current Project of the selected Organization, with their Headers, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected VM: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions:</description></item><item><title>Object Storage Credentials</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/object-storage-credentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/object-storage-credentials/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, delete and instructions for other steps to manage an Object Storage Credentials in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Object Storage page Create Object Storage credentials Show secret key Re-generate secret key Delete Object Storage credentials Object Storage page To get to the Object Storage page, select the Storage from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu and click the Object Storage TAB: On this page you can find all created Object Storage credentials in the current Project with their Headers, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Object Storage credentials: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions:</description></item><item><title>Access K8S Cluster</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/kubernetes/accessing-kuber/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/kubernetes/accessing-kuber/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of several ways how to access a Kubernetes Cluster created in Cloud Console
Table of contents Prerequisites Get access from Ubuntu VM to K8S Cluster using CLI User Get access from Centos VM to K8S Cluster using CLI User Connect to Cluster Master-Node via SSH Prerequisites In this article we will assume, that we have already created the following resources, that refer to the Project named dev1 that was created in the Organization named Test-Shop:</description></item><item><title>Access Linux VM</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/compute/connect-linux-vm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/compute/connect-linux-vm/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to connect to the Linux Virual Machine created in the Cloud Console using the SSH Protocol
Table of contents Prerequisites Configuring Firewalls Connect using SSH Prerequisites In this article we will assume, that we have already created the following resources, that refer to the Project named dev1 that was created in the Organization named Test-Shop:
SSH Key, that was created with the next parameters: Name: mykey; Public key is placed on the Linux VM during its creation; Private Key was copied to the clipboard and saved on the local system in the next text file (for example: ~/.</description></item><item><title>Firewalls</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/firewalls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/firewalls/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, edit and delete Firewalls in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Firewalls page Create Firewall Edit Firewall Delete Firewall Firewalls page To get to the Firewalls page, select the Security from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu and click the Firewalls TAB: On this page you can find default Firewall, all your own Firewalls created in the current Project, and the Firewalls created during Cluster creation, with their Headers, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Firewall: All VMs have a default Firewall which is applied to every VM.</description></item><item><title>Networks</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/network/networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/network/networks/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, edit and delete Networks in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Networks page Create Network Edit Network Delete Network Networks page To get to the Networks page, select the Networks from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu: On this page you can find the default public Network, all your own Networks created in the current Project, and the Networks created during Cluster creation, with their Headers, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Network: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions, but isn&amp;rsquo;t active for default public Network:</description></item><item><title>Organizations</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/organizations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/organizations/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create a new Organization and how to manage it in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Organizations page Create Organization Edit Organization Delete Organization Organizations page If you are a new user and have just created new account, you will be automatically redirected to the Organizations page, where you can create your first Organization or find a list of Organizations, to which Projects your User has access as a Member:</description></item><item><title>Ventus Console 2.4.5</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/release-notes/ventus-console2.4.5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/release-notes/ventus-console2.4.5/</guid><description>Successfully delivered to Production: 07.04.2021
Ventus Console 2.4.5 was successfully delivered to Production.
Here are the list of updates:
“Create VM” dialog was changed: Added ability to create VM from volume – volume should be in available state and it will be attached to the new VM. Added ability to create VM from snapshot – new volume will be created from the snapshot and will be attached to the new VM.</description></item><item><title>Working with OpenStack API</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/tutorials-advanced/working-with-openstack-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/tutorials-advanced/working-with-openstack-api/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to work with OpenStack API using the Ventus Cloud Account.
Table of contents Introduction Configure credentials file  Dot source credentials file Run test commands Change region Find resources Conclusion Introduction We encourage clients to use CLI Users to work directly with OpenStack API, but it has a limitation - it&amp;rsquo;s bonded to the specific project in the specific region.</description></item><item><title>Access Windows VM</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/compute/connect-windows-vm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/compute/connect-windows-vm/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to connect to the Windows Virtual Machine created in the Cloud Console using the Remote Desktop Protocol
Table of contents Prerequisites Configuring Firewalls Connect using RDP Prerequisites In this article we will assume, that we have already created the following resources, that refer to the Project named dev1 that was created in the Organization named Test-Shop:
Windows Virtual Machine - that was created with the next parameters and has IP: 185.</description></item><item><title>Administrators</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/identity-management/administrators/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/identity-management/administrators/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to add a new Administrator to the Organization, how to transfer the Organization to another User and how to remove Administrator from the Organization in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Administrators page Add Administrator Resend Invitation Delete Invitation Transfer Organization Remove Administrator Administrators page To see information about Administrators of the Organization and to manage them, you can only if your User Role in this Organization is an Administrator or Owner.</description></item><item><title>Firewall Rules</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/firewall-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/firewall-rules/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, delete Firewall Rules and instructions for other steps to manage Firewall Rules in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Firewall Rules page Firewall Rules Characteristics Create Firewall Rule Firewall Rule details page Delete Firewall Rule Firewall Rule for SSH Protocol Firewall Rule for RDP Firewall Rules page To get to the Firewall Rules page, click on the Name of the corresponding Firewall on the Firewalls page: On this page you can find:</description></item><item><title>Organization's management over API</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/tutorials-advanced/org-management-over-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/tutorials-advanced/org-management-over-api/</guid><description>On this page, you can find the workflow for management of your Organization in the Ventus Cloud using API.
Table of contents Required endpoints Example using CURL Example using Postman Required endpoints auth.ventuscloud.eu - use it to get ID and Access tokens from basic credentials api.ventuscloud.eu - use it to work with organization&amp;rsquo;s resources  Example using CURL Get ID and Access tokens
To get ID and Access tokens.</description></item><item><title>Subnets</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/network/subnets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/network/subnets/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, edit and delete Subnets in Cloud Console.
Table of contents Subnets page Create Subnet Edit Subnet Delete Subnet Subnets page To open the Subnets page, go to Networks page and click on the Name of the corresponding Network: On this page you can find:
panel with available quick actions for the selected Network: all created Subnets, related to the selected Network, with their Headers, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Subnet: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions for the selected Subnet:</description></item><item><title>Ventus Console 2.4.4</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/release-notes/ventus-console2.4.4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/release-notes/ventus-console2.4.4/</guid><description>Successfully delivered to Production: 25.03.2021
Ventus Console 2.4.4 was successfully delivered to Production.
Here are the list of updates:
MariaDB was added as DBaaS – all DBaaS UI was changed to support multiple DB engines VM Console logs were added to VM details – might be useful for customers to troubleshoot Linux VMs “Download RDP” action was removed for non-Windows VMs – a leftover bug, now fixed Image information was added to VM details Max length of organization name was changed to 255 chars Max length of cli user name was changed to 218 chars Max length of project name was changed to 27 chars Action to create Volume from Snapshot was added to the Storage -&amp;gt; Snapshots page .</description></item><item><title>Advanced network scenarios</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/tutorials-advanced/advanced-network-scenarios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/tutorials-advanced/advanced-network-scenarios/</guid><description>On this page we will discuss scenarios, that can help you to build software upgrade friendly and fault-tolerant cloud infrastructure.
Most of the topics described below considered advanced. Basic Linux and Networking skills are required. Please contact support if you need guidance and best practices for your specific use case.
Most of the features described below are in beta state, thus not available at the Console portal, and can be configured through CLI and IaC tools like Terraform and Ansible.</description></item><item><title>VM's Firewalls</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/manage-firewalls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/manage-firewalls/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to manage Firewalls related to the selected Virtual Machine in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents VM&amp;rsquo;s NETWORKS &amp;amp; SECURITY TAB Add Firewall Remove Firewall VM&amp;rsquo;s NETWORKS &amp;amp; SECURITY TAB To find all Firsewall, related to the selected Virtual Machine, you need:
open the Virtual Machines page - for this select the Virtual Machines from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu: open the Virtual Machine details page - for this click on the Name of the corresponding Virtual Machine: open the NETWORKS &amp;amp; SECURITY page of this VM - for this click on the NETWORKS &amp;amp; SECURITY TAB:</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/projects/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create a new Project, and how to manage them in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Projects page Create Project Edit Project Delete Project Add Users to Project Projects page To see information about Projects of the Organization and to manage them, you can only if your User Role in this Organization is an Administrator or Owner.</description></item><item><title>The Site to Site IPSec VPN</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/tutorials-advanced/site-to-site-ipsec-vpn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/tutorials-advanced/site-to-site-ipsec-vpn/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to configure Site to Site IPSec connection between the Ventus Cloud Regions.
Table of contents Prerequisites Configure Site to Site IPSec connection Strongswan useful commands Capture traffic Disable port-security Preparing client side Verifying connectivity Prerequisites Create a private network in each region. How to create a network see the articles - Networks and Subnets Create two VMs in private and public networks based on Ubuntu 18.</description></item><item><title>VM's Networks and Interfaces</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/network/manage-networksinterfaces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/network/manage-networksinterfaces/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to manage Networks and Interfaces related to the selected Virtual Machine in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents VM&amp;rsquo;s NETWORKS &amp;amp; SECURITY TAB Add Interface Remove Interface VM&amp;rsquo;s NETWORKS &amp;amp; SECURITY TAB To find all Networks and Interfaces related to the selected Virtual Machine, you need:
open the Virtual Machines page - for this select the Virtual Machines from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu: open the Virtual Machine details page - for this click on the Name of the corresponding Virtual Machine: open the NETWORKS &amp;amp; SECURITY page of this VM - for this click on the NETWORKS &amp;amp; SECURITY TAB:</description></item><item><title>Volumes</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/volumes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/volumes/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, edit, delete Volumes and instructions for other steps to manage Volumes in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Volumes page Create Volume Attach Volume Detach Volume Edit Volume Extend Volume Delete Volume Volumes page To get to the Volumes page, select the Storage from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu and click the Volumes TAB: On this page you can find all your own Volumes, created in the current Project, and the Volumes created during Cluster and VM creation, with their Headers, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Volume: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions:</description></item><item><title>VM's Volumes</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/manage-volumes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/manage-volumes/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to manage Volumes related to the selected Virtual Machine in Cloud Console.
Table of contents VM&amp;rsquo;s VOLUMES TAB Attach Volume Detach Volume Edit Volume Extend Volume VM&amp;rsquo;s VOLUMES TAB To find all Volumes, related to the selected Virtual Machine, you need:
open the Virtual Machines page - for this select the Virtual Machines from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu: open the Virtual Machine details page - for this click on the Name of the corresponding Virtual Machine: open the VOLUMES page of this VM - for this click on the VOLUMES TAB: On this page you can find all Volumes, attached to the corresponding VM, with their Headers, Attach button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Volume: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions:</description></item><item><title>Groups</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/identity-management/groups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/identity-management/groups/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create and manage a new Group in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Groups page Create Group Configure Group Manage Users in Group Manage Projects in Group Edit Group Delete Group Groups page Using Groups in the Cloud Console you can add additional Users to the Project.
To get to the Group page, select the Groups from the side-bar menu.</description></item><item><title>Snapshots</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/snapshots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/snapshots/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, edit, delete Snapshots and how to create Volumes from the Snapshots in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Snapshots page Create Snapshot Create Volume from Snapshot Edit Snapshot Delete Snapshot Snapshots page To get to the Snapshots page, select Storage from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu and click the Snapshots TAB: On this page you can find all created Snapshots with their Headers, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Snapshot: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions:</description></item><item><title>SSH Keys</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/ssh-keys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/ssh-keys/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, delete SSH Keys and instructions for other steps to manage SSH Keys in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents SSH Keys page Create SSH Key Pair Add Public Key Copy Public Key Delete SSH Key Pair SSH Keys page To get to the SSH Keys page, select Security from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu and click the SSH Keys TAB: On this page you can find all created SSH Keys with their Headers, Create and Add buttons, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Keypair: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions with the selected Keypair:</description></item><item><title>VM's Snapshots</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/manage-snapshots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/manage-snapshots/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to manage Snapshots, related to the selected Virtual Machine, in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents VM&amp;rsquo;s SNAPSHOTS TAB Create Snapshot Edit Snapshot Delete Snapshot VM&amp;rsquo;s SNAPSHOTS TAB To find all Snapshots, related to the selected Virtual Machine, you need:
open the Virtual Machines page - for this select the Virtual Machines from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu: open the Virtual Machine details page - for this click on the Name of the corresponding Virtual Machine: open the SNAPSHOTS page of this VM - for this click on the SNAPSHOTS TAB: On this page you can find all Snapshots, related to the corresponding VM, with their Headers, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Snapshot: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions:</description></item><item><title>CLI Users</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/cli-users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/cli-users/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, edit, delete CLI Users and instructions for other steps to manage CLI Users in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents CLI Users page Create CLI User Download RC File Edit CLI User  Change the password Delete CLI User  CLI Users page To get to the CLI Users page, select the Security from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu and click the CLI Users TAB: On this page you can find all created CLI Users, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected CLI User: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions with the selected CLI User:</description></item><item><title>Images</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/custom-images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/storage/custom-images/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to find list of default Images in the Cloud Console and how to create and delete custom Images.
Table of contents Images page Custom Images Prerequisites Get Images list Create custom Image Delete custom Image Images page To get to the Images page, select the Storage from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu and click the Images TAB: On this page you can find all default and custom Images, with their Headers and Search bar: Custom Images The Cloud Console functionality allows to upload custom Images to the system, which will be available for all resources in the current Project.</description></item></channel></rss>