<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on Ventus Docs</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on Ventus Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 01:53:09 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Account</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/account/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create and manage a new user account in teh Cloud Console.
Table of contents Registration Manage Account Edit Account Change password Set authenticator Find all sessions Login and Logout Registration To start work in the Cloud Console, firstly, you need to register a new account, for this do the following:
follow the Authorization page of the Cloud Console - console.</description></item><item><title>Organizations</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/organizations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/organizations/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create a new Organization and how to manage it in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Organizations page Create Organization Edit Organization Delete Organization Organizations page If you are a new user and have just created new account, you will be automatically redirected to the Organizations page, where you can create your first Organization or find a list of Organizations, to which Projects your User has access as a Member:</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/getting-started/projects/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create a new Project, and how to manage them in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Projects page Create Project Edit Project Delete Project Add Users to Project Projects page To see information about Projects of the Organization and to manage them, you can only if your User Role in this Organization is an Administrator or Owner.
To see information about created Projects in the Organization or create more Projects in it, you need on the Organizations page click on the Name of the appropriating Organization: This action will open additional sections on the side-bar menu and redirect you to the Projects page, where you can find all created Projects, related to the selected Organization with their Headers, Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Project: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions:</description></item></channel></rss>