<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DATABASES on EWW | ITandTEL Cloud Docs</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/databases/</link><description>Recent content in DATABASES on EWW | ITandTEL Cloud Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/databases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Databases</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/databases/databases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/databases/databases/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, edit, delete Databases and instructions for other steps to manage Databases in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents Databases page Create Database Database details page Edit Database Reset Database Password Delete Database Please be aware that the Database-as-a-Service feature in the Cloud Console is currently in beta. This means it has not been fully tested across all use cases but aims to provide a user-friendly way to manage a variety of databases.</description></item><item><title>Database's Custom Options</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/databases/database-custom-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/databases/database-custom-options/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of what is database&amp;rsquo;s Custom Options, how to manage them in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents Introduction Edit Database&amp;rsquo;s Custom Options PostgreSQL MySQL MariaDB Introduction Database&amp;rsquo;s Custom Options are a feature provided to modify options of your database. You can edit various settings such as max connections, WAL sender timeout, streaming delay, etc. depending on the database type.</description></item><item><title>Database's Replicas</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/databases/database-replicas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/databases/database-replicas/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of what is database&amp;rsquo;s Replica, how to create and manage them in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents Introduction Make Database&amp;rsquo;s Replica Delete Database&amp;rsquo;s Replica Introduction Database&amp;rsquo;s Replicas are a feature provided to ensure the security of your databases. In the Cloud Console, you can create up to 5 replicas of your database in different projects, across one or multiple regions.</description></item><item><title>Database's Backups</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/databases/database_backups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/databases/database_backups/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of what is database&amp;rsquo;s Backups, how to create it and how to restore Database from its Backup in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents Introduction Link Database to the S3 Storage Configure the Scheduler for Database Backups Create Immediate Database Backup Restore Database from Backup Introduction Database&amp;rsquo;s Backups offer an additional layer of security for your databases, similar to Database&amp;rsquo;s Replicas.</description></item></channel></rss>