<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Identity Management on Ventus Docs</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/identity-management/</link><description>Recent content in Identity Management on Ventus Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 01:53:09 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/identity-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Administrators</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/identity-management/administrators/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/identity-management/administrators/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to add a new Administrator to the Organization, how to transfer the Organization to another User and how to remove Administrator from the Organization in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents Administrators page Add Administrator Resend Invitation Delete Invitation Transfer Organization Remove Administrator Administrators page To see information about Administrators of the Organization and to manage them, you can only if your User Role in this Organization is an Administrator or Owner.</description></item><item><title>Groups</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/identity-management/groups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/identity-management/groups/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create and manage a new Group in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents Groups page Create Group Configure Group Manage Users in Group Manage Projects in Group Edit Group Delete Group Groups page Using Groups in the Cloud Console you can add additional Users to your Project.
To get to the Group page, select the Groups from the side-bar menu: On this page you can find all created Groups, related to the selected Organization with the Create button, Search bar, and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Group: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions:</description></item></channel></rss>