<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IMAGES on EWW | ITandTEL Cloud Docs</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/images/</link><description>Recent content in IMAGES on EWW | ITandTEL Cloud Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 01:53:09 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/images/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Images</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/images/custom-images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/images/custom-images/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to find list of default Images in the Cloud Console and how to create and delete custom Images.
Table of contents Table of contents Images page Custom Images Prerequisites Get Images list Create custom Image Delete Custom Image Create image from Snapshot Images page To get to the Images page, select the Storage from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu and click the Images TAB: On this page you can find all default and custom Images: Custom Images The Cloud Console functionality allows to upload custom Images to the system, which will be available for all resources in the current Project.</description></item><item><title>Create Image from Snapshot</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/images/image-from-snapshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/images/image-from-snapshot/</guid><description>On this page we will discuss the workflow, that can help you to create an Image from Snapshot.
Table of contents Table of contents Prerequisites Workflow Prepare Snapshot Create Volume from Snapshot Create Image from Volume Prerequisites In this article we will assume, that we have already created the following resources, that refer to the Project named Test-Project that was created in the Organization named Test-Organization:
CLI User (Name: test-conn) - which RC file has already been loaded; Ubuntu Virtual Machine (IP: 185.</description></item><item><title>Share Images between Projects</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/images/share-images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/images/share-images/</guid><description>On this page, we will discuss a workflow to help you to share Images between Projects in the same Region.
Table of contents Table of contents Prerequisites Workflow Share Image with another Project Accept shared Image Unshare Image Prerequisites In this article, we will assume that we have already created two Projects, belonging to different Organizations, but to the same Region, and the following resources within these Projects:
Project 1 named dev-1, that was created in the Organization named Test1 and related to the Vienna Region, with the following resources: CLI User named dev1CLIuser and which RC file has already been loaded; Ubuntu Virtual Machine - IP: 185.</description></item><item><title>Transfer Images between Regions</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/images/transfer-images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/images/transfer-images/</guid><description>On this page, we will discuss a workflow to help you to transfer Images between Projects in the different Regions.
Table of contents Table of contents Prerequisites Workflow Prepare custom Image Save custom Image Upload custom Image Prerequisites In this article, we will assume that we have already created two Projects, belonging to different Regions, and the following resources within these Projects:
Project-1 named v-dev, that related to the Vienna Region, with the following resources:</description></item></channel></rss>