<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infrastructure as code on EWW | ITandTEL Cloud Docs</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/iac/</link><description>Recent content in Infrastructure as code on EWW | ITandTEL Cloud Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/iac/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pulumi</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/iac/pulumi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/iac/pulumi/</guid><description>On this page, you can find essential steps and code for starting with Pulumi and Cloud, from installation to advanced deployment scenarios, highlighting the benefits of infrastructure as code (IaC) for simplifying and automating cloud infrastructure management.
Table of contents Table of contents Prerequisites Basic virtual machine setup Complex virtual machine setup Basic Kubernetes setup Prerequisites Pulumi installation - https://www.pulumi.com/docs/install Create CLI user - https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/cli-users Save credentials in Pulumi secrets - In our scenario, we utilize the Pulumi CLI to securely store credentials.</description></item><item><title>Terraform</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/iac/terraform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/iac/terraform/</guid><description>On this page, you can find essential steps and code for starting with Terraform and Cloud, from installation to advanced deployment scenarios, highlighting the benefits of infrastructure as code (IaC) for simplifying and automating cloud infrastructure management.
Table of contents Table of contents Prerequisites Prepare Terraform environment Basic virtual machine setup Complex virtual machine setup Basic Kubernetes setup Prerequisites Terraform installation - https://developer.hashicorp.com/terraform/install Create CLI user - https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/security/cli-users Install CLI client - https://docs.</description></item></channel></rss>