<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NETWORKING on EWW | ITandTEL Cloud Docs</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/</link><description>Recent content in NETWORKING on EWW | ITandTEL Cloud Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 01:53:09 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Networks</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/networks/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, edit, delete Networks and instructions for other steps to manage Networks in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents Networks page Create Network Create Subnet Edit Network Delete Network Attach Network Interface to the VM Networks page To get to the Networks page, select the Networking from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu and click the Networks TAB:: On this page you can find the default public Network, all your own Networks created in the current Project, and the Networks created during Cluster creation, with the Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Network: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions, but isn&amp;rsquo;t active for default public Network:</description></item><item><title>Floating IPs</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/floating-ips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/floating-ips/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, associate, edit, delete Floating IPs and instructions for other steps to manage Floating IPs in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents Floating IP Floating IPs page Create Floating IP Associate/Disassociate Floating IP Edit Floating IP Delete Floating IP Floating IP Floating IP is an IP address allocated from Public network range by request and associated with specific project.</description></item><item><title>Routers</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/routers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/routers/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, edit, delete Routers and how to manage Interfaces inside them in Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents Routers Routers page Create Router Add Interface to the Router Add custom Route to the Router Edit Router Delete Router Routers Router is an important infrastructure component that can come in handy when you need to:
Provide access to the internet for instances provisioned in a private network; Interconnect two or more networks; Manage routes for traffic in advanced network scenarios; Routers page To get to the Routers page, select the Networking from the VIRTUAL DATACENTER block in the side-bar menu and click the Routers TAB: On this page you can find all Routers created in the current Project, with the Create button, Search bar and Actions icon, which opens a list of available management actions for the selected Routers: Actions icon opens the next list of available management actions for the selected Router:</description></item><item><title>Subnets</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/subnets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/subnets/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to create, edit, delete Subnets and instructions for other steps to manage Subnets in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents Subnets page Create Subnet Edit Subnet Delete Subnet Connect Subnets Subnets page To open the Subnets page, go to Networking page and click on the Name of the corresponding Network: On this page you can find:</description></item><item><title>VM's Networks and Interfaces</title><link>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/manage-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.ventuscloud.eu/products/networking/manage-networks/</guid><description>On this page, you can find an explanation of how to manage Networks and Interfaces, related to the selected Virtual Machine, from the the Virtual Machine details page in the Cloud Console.
Table of contents Table of contents VM&amp;rsquo;s NETWORKS &amp;amp; SECURITY TAB Add Interface Remove Interface Associate/Disassociate Floating IP VM&amp;rsquo;s NETWORKS &amp;amp; SECURITY TAB To find all Networks and Interfaces related to the selected Virtual Machine, you need:</description></item></channel></rss>